Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching.
Hello! This time I'm joined by Ichika Arisawa from Juice-Juice and Ori Yagishi from
and Ori Yagishi from Tsubaki Factory.
We're going to show you the two of them this time, so please bear with us until the end.
This is the first episode of the year 2024! Stay!
I know it's a little late, but Happy New Year! And the day before yesterday was Coming of Age Day, wasn't it?
As of this recording, I haven't had my Coming-of-Age Day yet, but I, Yagi, went to take a pre-shoot for my furisode (long-sleeved kimono).
I'll tell you what kind of furisode I wore.
I wore a furisode that used a lot of classic colors and had some pictures of cranes on it.
I wore a furisode that had a little bit of individuality within the classic atmosphere.
What would you like to wear, Ichika?
I would like to wear a light blue and yellow furisode.
The reason is that light blue is my member's color.
Yellow has been my favorite color since I was a child, and I have sold it to many people.
I don't know how light blue and yellow would work together, but
I would like to try it on.
Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us has started!
I belong to Tsubaki Factory, which is in Team A with Morning Musume 24 and Beyonce.
Juice-Juice is in Team B with Angulum and Ochanomama. I am challenging to be a member of the dance team for the first time in this tour.
It was very difficult to remember the choreography in the rehearsal stage, and even more difficult to dance the choreography well.
I'm trying my best to create a cool atmosphere, so I'd like you all to see my performance.
Yes, Team B is still in the rehearsal stage.
We are still in the rehearsal stage, but the first thing that comes to my mind when I hear the names JuiceJuice, Angstrom, and Ochanoma is individuality.
Of course, the group has its own individuality, but each member has a very distinct pastel color.
My impression is that they have distinct personalities, and I am really looking forward to seeing how the clash of personalities will come together.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look at the video.
Let's do our best to keep up with BIN!
Dancing Shinken Exciting!
ED
I can't find it, I can't put it up, I can't find it, I can't put it up, Love Feria
I want to know more
Everybody Ah Yeah!
It's a coincidence that we met, it's a fact
Passion and reason, like the fate of a star
It's you, it's you, it's you, it's you, it's you
I'm getting more and more encounters with you
Sparkling Sneak Peek Rice
I'm late, I'm late, I want to meet you
I'd love to meet you, I'd love to meet you, I'd love to meet you...
But all I want to know is what you want to know
Let's ask him.
I can't find it. I don't know.
LOVE FAILURE
Not today. Not today.
I can't find it. I don't know.
LOVE FAILURE
Not today. Not today.
What I want to know
Everybody
Chocho
I can't find it, I can't find it, I can't find it, I can't find it, Love Fairy Ah
I don't know how, I can't have it Love Fairy Ah
I can't find it I can't find it I can't find it I can't find it I can't find it
I don't know, I can't have it Love Fairy Ah
I want to fall in love I want to throw it away Love Fairy Ah
Yeah, sometimes it's all I got
Love Terrier
I laughed so hard
On the train on the way home
LOVETERIA
What I want to know
Everybody
OK!
Subtitle & Subtitle Kyou
I'd like to drink warm cocoa.
Chika Aoi Arisa of JuiceJuice and Ori Yagishi of Tsubaki Factory present Halo ! sta!
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
What are you going to do now that the new year has come?
I'd like to make a video of myself singing "Kransik" on SNS.
Last year, we held our first overseas solo live concert
The first thing that comes to mind when I look back on our live shows in Hong Kong and Taiwan is
Food
On February 21, our first new album after joining the band
3rd Moment will be released on February 21!
What kind of Shiori Yagi do you think we can expect from this album?
The ever-growing Yagishiori.
What is your favorite dish now?
Mochi cheese omelette
What is the perfect word for Tsubaki Factory now that it has been 2 months since the new formation?
Wachawacha!
The thing I'm most worried about is
The first thing that comes to mind when I see you at your first solo overseas concert is food.
What did you eat?
In Hong Kong, I was given a solid meal that was pretty much like Koros food.
I had a good meal in Hong Kong, which was like Koros food.
Pigeon's chicks, abalone, and so on.
I was served food that I had never eaten before.
I also remember that I was served food that I had never eaten before, such as pigeon chicks and abalone.
In Taiwan, we were served baked or steamed parcels, baked eringi mushrooms, and fruit.
I also remember eating baked and steamed xiaolongbao, eringi mushrooms, and fruit, which I had never had before.
It had a different sweetness from Japanese fruit.
It was very sweet and very delicious.
It was the first thing that came to my mind.
It's so cute!
Thank you very much.
One more thing, about the classical singing videos...
Is there a difference in vocalization and other things?
It's totally different.
I see.
It's very different from a sensory point of view.
I think the listener can feel the difference as well.
The range you can produce is also very different.
I'm not sure if it's new to me.
I don't know if it's right to call it new, but I think it's a little different.
I hope you will be able to see a side of me that I have not been able to show you very often.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Questions for Icika will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! STE!
GETCHU!
I wonder if it's the summer
WA-CHAN WA-CHAN WA-CHAN WA-CHAN WA-CHAN WA-CHAN WA-CHAN Tea Auntie
Auntie Tea. First album Channel 1 is now on sale!
I'm Rikako Sasaki from Angeleum.
As I announced the other day,
Project after this year's spring tour.
Yes, I've been a member of Hello! Project for about 11 years including trainees,
Project for about 11 years, including the time as a trainee,
I have learned a lot of things in those 11 years,
I have learned many things during my 11 years in Hello!
I have learned a lot during my 11 years in the project, including my time as a trainee,
I realized during these 11 years that I really like expression in addition to singing and dancing.
I want to expand my expression beyond singing and dancing.
It is my dream to expand my range. It's more like a desire.
These things have been happening more and more, little by little,
That is the reason why I decided to leave the company after graduation.
So after graduation, I would like to broaden my range as an artist,
I have always put a lot of effort into dancing and singing,
I don't want to quit,
I don't want to say anything here that will make you expect more from me,
I don't want to say anything here that would make you expect more from me, but I would like to stand in front of you all the time,
I will never disappear from your presence,
I will never disappear from your sight, so please don't worry.
I will never disappear from your sight, so please don't worry,
Project, but I will continue to be Rika Sasaki for a long time to come,
I would be very happy if you all could support me. Thank you very much for your support.
Project concert has started.
I am thinking that the day will come when I will perform my last Hello!
Project concert,
Project, but I still don't really feel like I'm graduating yet, and I'm taking this picture because today is the first day of the concert,
I hope I can keep the excitement going until the very end.
This time, we were divided into three teams, not all of us,
Tea Horse, Juice!
I hope that everyone will be able to see the goodness of each and every team in this Hello!
I will do my best until the end.
Thank you for your continued support.
I am Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice.
Project concert for me, as I will graduate from Juice-Juice after this year's spring tour.
Project, so this time, the three groups of Hello!
Project will be divided into two groups, and they will perform alternately,
Last time we toured as "2 of us",
I'm looking forward to seeing Juice-Juice, Angstrom, and Ochanoma in each show, and I've never had a chance to talk with them before,
I am also aware of the fact that I have not had many opportunities to talk with them before, and I am also aware of the fact that I am graduating,
I am not the type to go out of my way to talk to people, so I am looking forward to talking to the younger, newer members of the group,
I am excited to have the opportunity to talk with new, younger students.
Graduation is approaching, but I don't think about it too much in the group activities,
I don't think that I will be conscious of it in our group activities, and I don't think that I will be thinking about it as the last time or anything like that,
But I am sure that I will be able to feel it when we get closer to the end,
Until then, I hope to enjoy the activities of Juice-Juice.
I hope you will continue to support us.
I hope you will continue to support us. STE!
Next, I would like to ask a question to Icika-chan.
I'll do my best.
Icika-chan turned 20 years old on the 23rd of last month.
What kind of 20s do you want to spend?
I want to spend my 20s like past, present and future.
What do you want to learn now?
Playing the saxophone.
It's been two and a half years since she joined the group.
Please give a catchphrase for the current Ichika Arisawa.
I'm Kazuka Arisawa, living in the moment.
What genre of music would you like to compose?
R&B
Cool!
There are only a few months left for the current group to be active.
Tell us about the current members and what you want to do.
We have decided to go on a bus tour, and I am really looking forward to it!
That sounds lovely.
Thank you.
I'm personally most interested in your catchphrase.
Arisawa Ichika, living in the moment.
What does it mean?
Well, I often look back on my past.
I live in the present based on the lessons I learned in my teenage years and what I learned through music.
But I don't think about the past without thinking about it.
I'm going to do the best I can now.
It's like a catchphrase I tell myself.
It's nice.
I just came up with that one.
Shiori Yagi gave me a catchphrase earlier.
What was it again?
Versatile and powerful girl.
That's it.
I thought it sounded like that, too.
Really? That's nice.
Thank you very much.
And when you asked me what kind of life I wanted to spend in my 20s.
I got past, present and future.
Why did you add the future?
Oh, I don't know.
I guess the 20s are a milestone, isn't it?
I don't know if I should call it a milestone, but...
I don't know...
You're no longer a teenager.
I'm not a teenager anymore.
I'm in my 20s, and I'm the most junior of my generation.
I feel like I'm going to do my best from now on.
That's nice.
Thank you very much.
Hello! Stay tuned for more after this!
BGM
This is Masashi Natsuyaki, and here we are at Hello Kitchen.
This time we have a member here with us.
I'm Damaralu from Juice-Juice. Nice to meet you.
I love cooking, so I'll do my best.
Nice to meet you, sir. Nice to meet you today, sir.
Good to meet you. Let's see what we're going to make this time.
Rainbow sushi rolls. I'm looking forward to it.
Here are the ingredients.
Have you ever made sushi rolls? I've seen my mom make them, but...
I've seen my mom make them, but I don't think I've ever done it by myself, so I'm really looking forward to it.
There are a lot of ingredients, and it's a rainbow of colors.
Let's have fun cooking with different flavors!
Let's have fun cooking!
So, what would you like to start with?
Well, we're going to make sushi rolls. We can't start without cooking rice, right?
No, we can't start.
Okay, so I'll start with No. 2. 360 cc.
360cc. Yes, that's good.
Okay, let's measure 360cc.
Rumor has it that Ruru-chan usually cooks.
She likes it.
But I like it. I'm not that good at it.
I mean, it's rumored that she makes a lot of bread.
I like it, but...
Today, you didn't check enough.
You were very nervous, weren't you?
I'll put it in. Yes, I'll put it in.
Yes, I'll put it in.
Yes, I'm in. It's in.
Now, let's cook the rice quickly.
Because it is unroasted rice.
So let's cook the rice quickly this time.
Yes, let's start.
Let's start.
Now, now, now, now, then, let's prepare the ingredients and proceed.
Okay, let's get the ingredients ready and get going.
Let's have them crack it open, like this,
Okay. Okay, let's get moving.
Okay.
Beautiful colored eggs. Really, really. Beautiful.
It's nice, isn't it? Color is important today, right?
That's right. It's a rainbow.
I want to layer as many different colors as possible.
Now, half. Half.
It's only half,
When you do it like this, it's like this.
It's like a swoosh.
You don't have to say it.
That's not true. Please tell me.
I feel safe today.
It's fine. Beautiful.
You're good.
As usual?
But you think it's the same?
As usual. As usual. It's always the same. As usual.
It's going to be kind of pillowy, isn't it?
Wait for it, let it dry rather well, and repeat.
It's good. It's good.
I'm already nervous.
Why did they have to look at me like that?
Indeed. I've never made such a banned ball while being watched.
Well, yeah.
That's true.
My hands are shaking.
I usually do it alone, but at home I can relax and cook.
You are used to it.
I get nervous. It's like this, isn't it? Hello kitchen.
Yes, everyone concentrates here.
Only at first, maybe.
Add torque!
Yay!
And look at the checker's work style!
We'll be using knives next, so...
Let's start with the cucumbers.
The cucumbers are to fit the size of the nori (seaweed)
This one was a little short.
I think it's about the right size.
It's perfect, so we're just going to drop the edges.
We'll just drop the end of the cucumber.
And then just drop it in the middle.
And then get the little spoon out.
The seeds are not very tasty.
They're kind of watery, so I want to take them out.
I see.
It's surprisingly easy to do.
Yes, it is.
If we lose today, I want to roll it twice.
Shall we make four?
Maybe we go to the middle.
And cut more.
You're very good at that, aren't you?
Like, "Yes.
Athletic conference.
Next, it's like unraveling a crabcake.
It's like it's been ripped open.
I'm just going to loosen it up a little bit, and then we'll go here.
Then we'll cut up the iburigakko and the cream cheese.
Shred the iburigakko.
Shredded
What is Juice-Juice's strongest team right now?
What are our strengths here?
But we've always been like a group that sings well.
We have often been told that we are good singers.
I would like to keep it that way.
But the younger members are very energetic.
I hope that girls who have their own specialties can make the most of them.
I'd like to make the best use of them.
For example, there is Isshika Arisaha who can play the violin.
Or a girl who can play the Japanese drums.
I think it would be great if that could be used in live performances.
I hope it will be used in live performances.
I really want you to do that.
So, today, the most difficult part is...
You're worried about the avocado.
Have you ever cut it?
No, I haven't.
But it's like a circle.
Put it in here and rotate it.
Shall we try it?
Is it hard? It's not hard.
Then you hit the seed, and then you start spinning it.
Beautiful avocado.
Got it.
That's good.
I can just peel it off by hand.
Let's peel it off.
Here's Miyamizu's point.
Is it this way? Is it right?
Is it right?
Slice the avocado and cut the misshapen part into thin strips.
You see here?
There's this.
It'll end up like this.
Like a crescent moon.
Only the part that doesn't have a hole in it.
Use it like a piece of sushi.
I'll just leave this part as it is.
I put it in the roll.
It just slides right in.
It's in good condition.
But I can see the hole.
Well, then...
Let's cut it here.
Here.
Bring it here.
Wrap this around.
And that one here.
It's as soft as cream cheese.
It's soft.
It's in good shape.
Smooth.
The color is beautiful.
Kaneko Tamago no Tamago has cooled down.
Let's cut it.
Yes, sir.
What do you usually do?
It always depends on the size.
I think you can cut it in half.
But it's a nice color.
It's really beautiful.
It's orange.
You're really, really good.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes.
It's perfect.
Now I'd like to make sushi rice.
Please put the cooked rice into the bat.
We have already prepared the ingredients for sushi rice today.
4 tablespoons for 2 cups.
Mix it as you cut it.
But at first
There is a lot of water in the rice.
I think I made a mistake.
It's totally fine.
Then spread it out.
It's all right now.
Sushi rice looks delicious.
I think it's good.
Finished.
Sushi rice is ready!
So this time, I cut the ingredients and the sushi rice.
So this time, we have just cut the ingredients and the sushi rice.
Next time, it will be finished.
It didn't take long!
I was so surprised at how skillful Yui was!
Let's have fun again next time!
Please look forward to the next time!
If you squeeze too hard, it will come out from the side.
So be gentle.
Okay, let me get it out a little bit.
I think that's good.
I don't know if I can eat it.
Is it all gone?
Please eat slowly.
This is Ichika Arisawa of Juice Chus.
and Ori Yagishi of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Stay!
This is the first "Halo! I'd like to announce our goals for this year as individuals and as a group.
Let's start from individual goals.
Se-no!
Yes, I'm Arisa. I, Arisa, want to be a good soil.
To be a good soil means to be a good dancer in live performance, for example, if there is a member who is good at dancing,
For example, if there is a member who is good at dancing, when she performs her solo dance, the members in the back may stand or do other dances, but she can make that dance of the member who is doing the solo dance grow.
I want to make that beautiful flower bloom, and I want to make that beautiful flower bloom in the song, in fake or in unison.
I want to be a person who can be a good foundation for the flower to bloom beautifully and find a good position instantly.
Sometimes I also want to try my best to be a beautiful flower.
It's wonderful, isn't it? The idea of becoming the soil.
The idea of becoming soil is quite interesting, and I think it's wonderful that you compared it to soil.
Thank you very much. And the finishing touch is the entrance to the Camellia Factory.
The reason why I chose the entrance to the Tsubaki Factory is because I want to share my strengths and interests with the public, and to build the Tsubaki Factory on the basis of them.
I would like to share my specialties and interests with you, and I hope that you will be inspired to build the Tsubaki Factory.
For example, as I mentioned earlier, I would like to make a video of myself singing classical music on sns.
I would like to do my best in the future to make people know about Tsubaki Factory.
Hello! Sta.
Next, let's announce our goals as a group.
My goal and GIGAOMO group's goal is to make many people aware of Tsubaki Factory.
The reason why we set this goal is because many of the members of Tsubaki Factory want to make Tsubaki Factory known to more people.
In order to increase the number of fans, we need to get more people to notice Tsubaki Factory, and then we can get more people to like Tsubaki Factory and become our fans.
I would like to increase the number of people who notice us first.
That's great!
Thank you very much.
My goal as a group is to make various flowers bloom.
I said earlier that we want to become soil.
If there are many flowers in bloom, a single flower is invisible from a distance, but if there are many beautiful flowers in bloom, even from a distance, they will have a presence and make people want to get closer to them.
That's why I want to make Juice Juice bloom with many flowers.
The idea that if there are a lot of flowers, they can be seen from a distance, so people will notice them is really wonderful.
We, Camellia Factory, will do our best to make many camellia flowers bloom.
Let's do our best in 2024, too!
Yes, ma'am.
NANANA...
The first time I spoke to you, my dear ones.
Don't dream too big and don't be someone else.
Thank you for looking at me with such a serious face.
And that's when our hearts began to resonate.
What's your feeling?
All across the country, Laura, we'll go on and on until we make this song ring.
We'll make it on our own.
How can we not do that already?
We'll be fine if we use it
♪ The cosmic chiampathy shining in our hearts
♪ We'll use it to make our hearts sing ♪
It's the first time we've hit a groove.
The timing is all over the place
Innocent personalities
Found each other
And still it's sad
Every day is a new year
If you want to take the pressure off
Taste it with bitterness
There must be someone waiting somewhere in the world
Let's get the wings of goose bumps again
With this singing voice
We, we, we will meet and spread happy-less, so that we can all sway together
We'll sing from the bottom of our hearts, repeating into the night Without muddying the tea, it'll always be a summer dream frenzy
We'll sing from the bottom of our hearts
We'll sing from our hearts again and again into the night
If you're alone, you'll never get started
We'll be fine if you tell them this way
I don't know about the emptiness that shines in my heart, but I have a premonition
Gutto kuyo, kuyo kuyo, kuyo kuyo, kuyo kuyo, kuyo kuyo
Crying with tears, this emptiness is engraved on my heart
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us is now underway.
Team A will perform in Sendai on January 13. Team B will perform in Osaka on January 20. Please come and see them.
Tsubaki Factory's new album "3rd Moment" will be released on February 21.
There are 4 new songs included in the album,
There are 4 new songs on the album, including a song written by Ai Shock of Shonanokaze and Takuya Nakajima, so I hope you will enjoy them.
Tsubaki Factory's major debut 7th anniversary live will be held on March 10 at Ichikawa City Cultural Hall.
I am really looking forward to it, so I would be happy if you could come.
I am also looking forward to seeing you at the "Carbon Neutral Movement 2024 by Satoyasato Preliminary Movement" to be held on March 30 and 31 at Makuhari Messe in Chiba Prefecture.
I am really looking forward to this one as well.
I am very much looking forward to it as well. Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time we were joined by Arisa Aoi Chika of Juice- Juice and Ori Yanagishita of Tsubaki Factory.
Farewell!